{
    "question": "Change these sentences into simple past tense.    a. All the\r\n\r\nstudents in this school clean all the part of their school to face the Independence day.\r\n\r\nb. Our\r\n\r\nheadmaster gives punishment to the students who don't wear uniform.\r\n\r\n\r\nBantu jawab kak. jgn ngasal ya kakk\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "All the students in this school cleaned all the part of their school to face the independence day<br><br>Our headmaster gave punishment to the students who did not wear uniform<br><br>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "<p>a. All the students cleaned all the part of their school to faced the independence day. </p><p></p><p></p><p>b. Our headmaster gave punishment to the students who didn&#039;t wear uniform. </p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "why-did-lamar-davis-roasted-franklin-explain-it-480",
            "question": "Why did Lamar Davis Roasted Franklin?\r\nexplain it!\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>where is the text? idk the answer without the text</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>mengapa lamar davis memanggang franklin? </p><p>jelaskan itu!</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "a-b-two-hundred-and-thirty-five-thousand-ahow-many-bho-239",
            "question": "A: .....?    B: Two hundred and thirty-five thousand\r\na.How many\r\nb.How much\r\nc.How are there\r\nd.How is there\r\ntolong jawab\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Jawaban yang benar adalah:</p><p>B. How much</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "B. How much<br>Maaf ya kalo salah xixix",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "hello-my-friend-my-name-is-fransiska-im-12-years-old-i-come-f-522",
            "question": "Hello my friend. My name is Fransiska. I'm 12 years old. I come from Solo. I live at jln. Yos Sudarso 19, Solo.    My hobby is reading. My favorite reading is comic. It is\r\nabourt sinchan.\r\n\r\n19. Where does Fransisca come from?\r\nJln. Kapten Tandean\r\nb. Jln. Yos Sudarso\r\nSolo\r\nd. Jln. Bima IX\r\n20. How old is Fransisca? She is ...\r\n12 years old\r\nc. 20 years old\r\nb. 2 years old\r\nd. 13 years old\r\n21. Does Fransisca like reading Novel?\r\na. No, she is not\r\nc. Yes, she is\r\nb. Yes, she does\r\nd. No, she doesn't\r\n22. What is her hobby?\r\na. Listening to music. c. Reading\r\nb. Playing footbal\r\nd. Watching TV\r\n23. Where does she live?\r\na. Jln. Slamet Riyadi c. Jln. Pattimura\r\nb. Jln. Yos Sudarso d. Jln. Anggrek\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>19. B</p><p>20. A</p><p>21. A</p><p>22. C</p><p>23. B</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu </p><p>#semangata belajar</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-problems-can-a-crowded-clutterred-or-small-living-space-t-c-737",
            "question": "What problems can a crowded clutterred or small living space t. create for a student?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>Masalah apa yang bisa menjadi ruang tamu yang berantakan atau sempit t. buat mahasiswa?</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "6-when-your-fathers-company-got-a-very-big-problem-you-send-hi-868",
            "question": "6.    When your father's company got a very big problem, you send him a.......\r\na. apology card\r\nb. Invitation card\r\nd. weeding card\r\nText for nomber 8-11\r\nMy name is Raditia. I went to BorobudurTemple last weekend. I went there with my\r\nclassmates and teachers. We went there by bus.It was a program of my school to learn\r\nIndonesia history.\r\nI was so amazed seeing the temple. It's so wonderful. It's Hindu-Buddhist temple. It's was\r\nbuilt in nith century by Sailendra dynasty. My friends and I really noticed our guide who told\r\nabout the history of th temple. The guide ,Mr Tom explained evey single thing about the temple\r\nvery clearly and detail. I also took several pictures in the temple.Beside I get knowledgeabout\r\nBorobudur temple.I enjoy the view.It's was my that I will never forget.\r\n8.\r\nWhat text s it?\r\na. Recount\r\nb. Descriptive\r\nd. Narrative\r\nc. Refort\r\n9.\r\nWho went to Borrobudur Temple last week?\r\na. Raditia\r\nb. Raditia's friends\r\nc. Raditia's, his classmates, and teachers\r\nd.\r\n10.\r\nWhat did Raditia take in theBorobudur Temple ?\r\na. Several pictures of Borobudur Temple\r\nb. A statue of buddha\r\nC. Some souveniers\r\nd. The stupa\r\n11.\r\na.\r\nb.\r\nWhy did they go Borobudur Temple ?\r\nTo take the Borobudur temple picture\r\nTo entertain the student after having final examination.\r\nTo learn Indonesia history\r\nTo spend a lo of money\r\nC.\r\nd.\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><h2>6.</h2><h2>When your father&#039;s company got a very big problem, you send him a.......</h2><h2>a. apology card</h2><h2>b. Invitation card</h2><h2>d. weeding card</h2><h2>Text for nomber 8-11</h2><h2>My name is Raditia. I went to BorobudurTemple last weekend. I went there with my</h2><h2>classmates and teachers. We went there by bus.It was a program of my school to learn</h2><h2>Indonesia history.</h2><h2>I was so amazed seeing the temple. It&#039;s so wonderful. It&#039;s Hindu-Buddhist temple. It&#039;s was</h2><h2>built in nith century by Sailendra dynasty. My friends and I really noticed our guide who told</h2><h2>about the history of th temple. The guide ,Mr Tom explained evey single thing about the temple</h2><h2>very clearly and detail. I also took several pictures in the temple.Beside I get knowledgeabout</h2><h2>Borobudur temple.I enjoy the view.It&#039;s was my that I will never forget.</h2><h2>8.</h2><h2>What text s it?</h2><h2>a. Recount</h2><h2>b. Descriptive</h2><h2>d. Narrative</h2><h2>c. Refort</h2><h2>9.</h2><h2>Who went to Borrobudur Temple last week?</h2><h2>a. Raditia</h2><h2>b. Raditia&#039;s friends</h2><h2>c. Raditia&#039;s, his classmates, and teachers</h2><h2>d.</h2><h2>10.</h2><h2>What did Raditia take in theBorobudur Temple ?</h2><h2>a. Several pictures of Borobudur Temple</h2><h2>b. A statue of buddha</h2><h2>C. Some souveniers</h2><h2>d. The stupa</h2><h2>11.</h2><h2>a.</h2><h2>b.</h2><h2>Why did they go Borobudur Temple ?</h2><h2>To take the Borobudur temple picture</h2><h2>To entertain the student after having final examination.</h2><h2>To learn Indonesia history</h2><h2>To spend a lo of money</h2><h2>C.</h2><h2>d.</h2><p></p><p>6.</p><p>When your father&#039;s company got a very big problem, you send him a.......</p><p>a. apology card</p><p>b. Invitation card</p><p>d. wedding card</p><p>Text for number 8-11</p><p>My name is Raditia. I went to Borobudur Temple last w</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "whatt-should-we-do-before-and-after-doing-something-838",
            "question": "Whatt Should we do before and after doing something?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>You can do anything Play, eat and study</p><p><strong></strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kevin-hi-you-look-lost-can-i-help-you-tourist-yes-im-t-994",
            "question": "Kevin : hi, you look lost. can i help you? tourist : yes, i\u2019m trying to get to the railway station. in the dialogue , we know that kevin \u2026",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>try to help the tourist.</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan: </p><p>hope you find this helpful^\u2022^</p><p></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "1-i-will-this-beautiful-scenery-2-a-traditional-song-ia-317",
            "question": "1. i will ... this beautiful scenery 2. ... a traditional song ia my hobby 3. let's.... with me. i will be romeo and you will be juliet",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1 capture</p><p>2 singing</p><p>3 act</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "we-happy-birthday-but-we-didnt-eat-cake-316",
            "question": "We \u2026. happy birthday but we didn\u2019t eat cake",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>celebrated. Correct Me If I Wrong  semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "this-dialog-is-for-question-no-57-sarah-look-mom-brought-us-a-360",
            "question": "This dialog is for question no 5.7    Sarah : Look, Mom brought us a kitten!\r\nOh my God, it's a Persian kitten. She is so cute,\r\nSarah\r\n: Yes, I like her big eyes and chubby cheeks. Look at her legs, they are short!\r\nFia : I love her snub nose the most!\r\n5. What animal is being described in the dialog?\r\nA. Dog\r\nD. Cat\r\nC. Rabbit\r\nB. Bird\r\n6\r\nThe animal in the dialog above has ....\r\nA small eyes\r\nB. short legs\r\nC. long nose\r\nD. flat chee!\r\n7. How do the speakers feel when they see the animal? They are\r\nA. gloomy\r\nB.calm\r\nC.mad\r\nD.glad\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>5. D. Cat</p><p>6. B. Short legs</p><p>7. D. Glad</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>5. B. Cat</p><p></p><p>6. B. Short legs</p><p></p><p>7.  D. Glad</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p><em>Semoga</em><em> </em><em>membantu</em><em> </em><em></em></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}